{
    "id": "7e5d55247dd243c6817e53310804137c",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Look",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Who will look .............................. your pets when you are on holiday?",
            "description": "To look after somebody is to take care of them.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e040fc00c0144e358837fd6308b6169b"
        },
        {
            "question": "If we have time we will have a look ............................... the city.",
            "description": "To look around a place is to explore it",
            "answers": [
                "around",
                "over",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c585ddaf505d4697be2ee865a3e33707"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will look ............................. all the applications before hiring someone.",
            "description": "To look at something is to consider it or examine it.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6791820c6dc243ffb1f82cff96c8e8e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is looking ............................. a hefty fine and jail term if he does not prove his innocence.",
            "description": "To look at something is to face it or confront it.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4d53d80251a549cbaa71fb2ff9571fc1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tears roll down my cheeks, whenever I look ............................... on my childhood.",
            "description": "To look back on something is to think about it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "back",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7868ca3a944a47d19995039702b337b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "When they became rich they began to look ................................ their poor neighbors.",
            "description": "To look down on somebody is to consider them inferior.",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "below",
                "down on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5cd2e8cb26cb40ab901c15f9669d3e2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you help me look ............................... my cat? She has been missing since morning.",
            "description": "To look for somebody or something is to search for them or it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a74415bec35d40a48b2efdce4dc910d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am really looking ............................... to becoming a mother.",
            "description": "To look forward to something is to be excited about something that will happen in the future.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "forwards",
                "forward"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ed8d313d024e40789694a0a42c57abfe"
        },
        {
            "question": "Julie looked ................................... us on her way home.",
            "description": "To look in on somebody is to pay them a short visit.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "in on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c34d8a2371304efb95c1542cf70959d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The supervisor has agreed to look ............................... the matter.",
            "description": "To look into something is to investigate it.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "up",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2332f205ebc44a4685c81e7036486b11"
        },
        {
            "question": "I looked ................................. as the children played in the park.",
            "description": "To look on is to watch an activity without getting involved.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "79c4c60e32484ad690b66fec674c60ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "Look ..........................! The floor is wet.",
            "description": "This is an expression used to warn someone to be careful.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "495b8d39ab5b44bf9db682f36399886c"
        }
    ]
}